tintup.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | TINT

## Introduction

TINT is a brand name of Hypemarks, Inc. TINT provides online services to help business customers find, curate, and display social media posts and other content in support of their marketing activities. Most of our customers are businesses or other organizations. TINT’s main office is in San Antonio, Texas and it offers its services to customers worldwide.

This Privacy Policy describes our policies for personal data that we collect and use for our own general business purposes.

We also have personal data in our possession that our customers have collected (either independently of our service, or using our search and filtering tools) and asked us to process for them as part of our services. We do not use this customer-controlled data for our own business purposes, but only as permitted by our customers in our agreements with them. We have included information below to describe our commitments to you if we have access to your data in our role as a data processor, but you should review the privacy statement of our customer to understand their privacy practices.

## How to Contact Us

Email: [privacy@tintup.com](mailto:privacy@tintup.com "Email us") or via mail: TINT – 122 East Houston St, San Antonio TX 78205.

Please contact us at this address if you have any questions about the information in this Privacy Statement or our handling of your personal data, or would like to access, amend, delete or take other action with regard to your personal data. We ask, however, that if we are in possession of your data solely as a data processor for our customer you first contact our customer with your request.

## Changes to Privacy Statement

We may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. We will manage your personal data in accordance with the Privacy Statement version that was published on the date that we collected the data about you. Prior versions of our Privacy Statement may be found at <https://github.com/filestack/tint-privacy-policy>.

## Definitions

These words have special meanings in this Privacy Policy:

  * **account** user means an individual who interacts with us as a representative of our customer;
  * **customer** means the business or other organization that establishes and account with us for the use of our services;
  * **services** means our online services for the discovery, curation, management and display of social media postings and other content;
  * **"site"** or **"website"** refers to www.tintup.com and any other website where this Privacy Policy is posted;
  * **social media user** means an individual whose posting or tweet on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or other social media platform is managed by our customer on our online curation platform;
  * **"visitor"** means an individual who visits our website, interacts with us at a trade show or other industry event, or communicates with us in some other way other than as an account user, social media user, or other content provider;
  * **"we"** , **"our"** and **"us"** refer to Hypemarks, Inc. dba TINT;
  * **"you"** and **"your"** refer to visitors, account users, and content providers.

## Data Collection Purposes

We collect personal data for the following purposes:

  * to improve our website and product offerings;
  * to market our services;
  * to manage our relationship with our customers and provide customer support; and
  * to provide services to our customers.

## Data Collection Methods

#### Automated data collection

We collect data about website visitors (including pre-login data of account users) using our web server logs and third party analytics services such as Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Segment, and HubSpot.

For example, our web server logs information such as your IP address, internet service provider, the time and duration of your visit on each page on the site, your browser type (including plug-ins), and information about your device, such as the operating system, time zone setting, and language setting. We may place a cookie on your browser to identify you as a return visitor if you visit our site more than once.

Please see How to **Opt Out of Online Data Collection** below for information on how to block cookies. We use data collected in this way to improve our website and product offerings. For example, we may use data that we collect to help us understand what part of our services offering is of interest to site visitors, or to help us make our site more appealing or easier to use.

#### Data provided by advertisers

If you arrive at our site by clicking on a link that is part of an advertisement on another site (including an advertisement on a social media platform), the advertising service will identify the link, enabling us to associate you with the advertising parameters we provided to the advertising service.

For example, we may ask an advertising service to target our ad to individuals that the ad service has identified as having a high interest in social media. If you arrive at our site by means of the link in that ad, we will be able to identify you as having a high interest in social media. We use this data to improve our website and product offerings, and to market our services. For example, this information helps us understand if our marketing campaigns are successful so that we can improve our marketing strategy.

See the section below captioned **Advertising Ecosystem Data** and **How to Opt Out of Online Data Collection**. Advertising services are responsible for the collection, use and disclosure of the data they provide to us in accordance with their published privacy policies.

#### Data provided by you as part of your communications with us

We collect personal data that you submit to us as part of a communication with us, such as via chat on our site, email, submission of a web form, telephone, or in person (such as at a meeting, trade show or other event). This may include your name, job title, job function, the organization you represent, email address, phone number, and other personal data that may choose to submit as part of the communication. We use contact information to respond to your communication (such as providing the information or support that you request), and may also use contact information to market our services to you. We may use other personal data included in the communication to improve our site or services, or improve our marketing strategies.

For example, we may use information about your job function or organization to understand who we should communicate with within your organization is a good target for our marketing efforts, or to decide what types of services to market to you or your organization.

#### Data provided by you or your organization to establish and maintain the TINT account

Our customers are required to name billing, administrative, technical and other types of service and account users who have authority to use our services and manage the customer’s account. We collect the name and business contact information of these account representatives, and will require each individual account representative to establish their own set of account credentials (user name and password). We will use this information to manage the account, such as to send invoices and other account communications, and authenticate individuals who use the services or request information or support on the customer’s behalf. If the customer wishes to integrate their social media accounts with our services, we will require the customer to provide the account credentials used by their representatives on those platforms. We will use those credentials to maintain a live sync between the social media platform and our curation platform as to the social media posts that our customers chooses to manage on our platform.

#### Marketing Partners and Resellers

We have relationships with other companies that help us market, sell and deliver our services, such as event planners. They may provide us with data of the type described above using the methods we describe. We may use that data for the purposes described above.

#### Combinations of data collected using different methods

We may combine data we collect using any of the methods described above, and use the combined data for the purpose of improving our site and products, marketing our services, or managing our relationship with our customer.

#### Data Integrity

We process personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. We regularly review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process the minimum personal information needed for the purpose collected. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information that we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our account users to update or correct their personal data whenever necessary.

#### Requests to access, amend, delete or restrict the use of your personal data

Please send us a request at privacy@filestack.com if you would like to know what personal data we have about you, or would like us to correct inaccurate data, delete your personal data, or restrict the use of your personal data. We commit to responding to your request promptly and honoring your reasonable requests. We will comply with all applicable legal requirements related to your requests, but please note that we are not required by law to delete or restrict the use of your data in a way that prevents us from complying with our legal obligations to our customer or that interferes with our reasonable record keeping as necessary to demonstrate compliance with our contracts and applicable law.

## Processor Data

Our services includes search and filtering tools that help our customers find public social media posts that are relevant to their products, and a dashboard that helps customers curate and manage social media posts as well as other public and non-public media files (such as the customer’s privately generated content). As part of providing these service we collect data on the customer’s behalf about social media users, such as their social media user name or handle, and may collect other data that the social media platform provider makes available such as the social media users IP address. We collect this data in accordance with the privacy requirements of the platform providers. You should view their privacy statements and user agreements for information about their privacy practices. Although we help our customers collect and manage this data, we do not control the use of this data and use it only as permitted by our agreement with our customer, generally to provide the services to them and related activities. Our customers use our dashboard to serve social media posts and other content on their websites and other displays, such as digital signs. We collect data about web users who interact with our customers websites on our customer’s behalf using web server logs and cookies. Our customers are responsible for making appropriate cookie disclosures and enabling any required cookie opt out process.

Some of our customers are subject to special data privacy laws, such as the General Data Protection Regulation adopted by the European Union in May 2018. Our commitments as a processor of data covered by these types of regulations are stated in our Data Processing Addendum.

Please contact us at the address above if you have questions or concerns regarding our processing of the data described in this Section. We ask, however, that your first contact our customer if you have a request to access, block, erase or take other action with respect to data that we have solely as a data processor for our customer.

## Disclosure

We have not sold or leased personal data, and will not sell or lease your personal data unless you give us your consent to do so.

We will not disclose your personal data to third parties except as follows:

#### Legal Reasons

When we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce our terms of use and other rights, or to protect the rights and safety of others.

This may include exchanging information with government regulatory or law enforcement agencies, or with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and legal compliance.

#### Sale of Business

As part of a sale of a sales of business assets where the purchaser needs the personal data to use the assets.

We may in the future sell all or part of our assets or be involved in a merger. We may provide the company that is seeking to acquire our business with access to personal data as part of their evaluation of our business, but will require them to maintain the personal data in confidence and use it only to evaluate our business. If we complete a transaction, it is customary to transfer personal data that is related to the purchased business assets to the purchaser.

#### Service Providers

We use the services of companies like the ones listed below to collect data on our behalf or to help us analyze, store, manage and otherwise process your personal data. Each of these companies commits in its contract with us to use the personal data only according to our contract with them or our other instructions as necessary to support our business. They are not authorized to use your personal data for any other purpose. They are not authorized to disclose your personal data to others except with our permission, and only if they require the others to comply with the same restrictions that apply to them.

  * Sendgrid - outgoing email
  * Zendesk - incoming email, support
  * DocuSign, HelloSign - E-signing
  * Stripe, bill.com - payment processing
  * Google - organization email and documents management provider
  * Google Analytics - analytics
  * Google Ads - advertising
  * Mixpanel - analytics
  * HubSpot marketing, landing pages, analytics
  * Salesforce – customer relationship management
  * Instapage - langing pages
  * Amazon AWS – Infrastructure provider, applications
  * Mode - business intelligence
  * Qualaroo - users feedback

## Advertising Ecosystem

We use online advertising services that enable a practice referred to as “online behavior advertising.” These services aggregate data about an individual’s behavior on many different sites and online services, and use that data to sell targeted advertising services. For example, we permit Google’s advertising services to collect data about your behavior on the TINT site, as do many other website operators who use Google’s ad services. Google combines the data about an individual that it collects from different sources, and uses this aggregate data to sell advertising services that target the display of ads to web users who meet certain behavioral criteria. Google does not disclose this aggregate data to TINT, but we are able to infer that users who interact with our ad meet the advertising criteria we provided. Google collects this data using cookies, web server logs (its own and its advertising customers), clear gifs and other online data collection techniques. See Online Data Collection Techniques and How to Opt Out of Online Data Collection.

## Online Data Collection Techniques

A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that is placed by a web server on the web visitor’s browser. Cookies are used to analyse visitors’ use of the website. For example, a website operator can use the cookie to identify the number of unique visitors to the site, whether or not those visitors are repeat visitors, and information about the visitor’s activity on the site, device and device settings. A tracking pixel, also known as a web bug or web beacon, is a small graphic (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) invisible to the eye, that is embedded in web content or email. When content that has an embedded web beacon is viewed, the browser will request content from a web server, which in turn will set a cookie.

## How To Opt Out Of Online Data Collection

You can manage browser cookies through your browser settings. The 'Help' feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, how to disable cookies, and when cookies will expire. If you disable all cookies on your browser, neither we nor third parties will transfer cookies to your browser. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some features and services may not work.

Our web server does not recognize or respond to any “do not track” setting you may have in your browser.

The third parties who we permit to collect data on our site have features that allow you to block their data collection via cookies. See their privacy policies and cookie policies:

Google Ads: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?/hl=en&gl=us&hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?/hl=en&gl=us&hl=en "Visit Google policies page")

## Communications Policy

If you do not wish to receive our email or other communications, please send your request to privacy@tintup.com. Please note that it may take up to ten days to remove your contact information from our marketing communications lists, so you may receive correspondence from us for a short time after you make your request.

## Children

Children are not permitted to use our site or services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on our Sites unless you have involved your parent or guardian. If we discover that we have information about a child we will delete that information. If you are the parent or guardian of a child and you believe we have personal data about the child without your consent, please contact us at the address appearing at the top of this page and we will delete that information.

## Security

TINT protects personal data from unauthorized use, disclosure, corruption and destruction using appropriate technical and organizational measures.

## Data Retention

We will retain your personal data only for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, and to comply with our legal obligations. We may retain your personal data for a longer period in the event of a complaint or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship with you.

## Privacy Shield

TINT complies with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. TINT has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

  * In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, TINT commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact us at: [privacy@tintup.com](mailto:privacy@tintup.com).
  * TINT has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. Data subjects in the EU and in Switzerland who do not receive timely acknowledgment of their complaint, or fee that their complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, should visit <https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/> for more information and to file a complaint. The services of the Better Business Bureau are provided at no cost to you.
  * Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. See <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.
  * The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over TINT’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.
  * As a Privacy Shield organization we remain liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if our agent processes your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless we proves that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
